MIKL WOLFE

510-501-5032 | wolfe@mikl.io github.com/chiefmikey | linkedin.com/in/miklwolfe

PROFIL F

Software engineer experienced in a large variety of full-stack languages and frameworks. Strong comprehension of advanced technologies and systems including DevOps. Extensive experience developing high-level implementations autonomously. Career began in UX/UI design and progressed into software engineering.

RECENT EXPERIENCE

Marketron | Full-Stack Software Engineer | 2022-2023

- Fulfilled a variety of needs and drove implementations across teams including QA and DevOps
- Substituted for engineering manager in client issues, deployments, sprint planning, etc.
- Supported new product features with technical design documentation and execution strategy

Marketron | Junior Software Engineer | 2022–2022

- Debugged and resolved time-sensitive client issues and prepared hotfixes for deployment
- Completed a shift-left developer testing course and demonstrated key takeaways to the team
- Collaborated closely with offshore resources across multiple front and back-end microservices

Independent Contract | Full-Stack Software Engineer | 2021

- Migrated an inefficient site to a scaleable React platform for a growing beverage company
- Increased load capacity of a site with heavy traffic for a startup in the cryptocurrency industry

PREVIOUS EXPERIENCE

Innovation Roundtable | UX/UI Designer | 2019–2021

- Strengthened user experience with refined web design and front-end optimizations
- Developed new platform features and content offered as resources to customers
- Highlighted performance and engagement with custom SEO and analytics reports

The Simon Collective | UX/UI Designer | 2017-2019

- Designed and implemented a web portfolio site to carefully represent the brand message
- Managed and maintained technical needs including domain DNS and hosting
- Refreshed branding and created clearly presented guidelines for future consistency

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Node, TypeScript, JavaScript, React, Redux, PostgreSQL, MongoDB, Express, Koa, Axios, Jest AWS, Docker, Webpack, GitHub Actions, Shell Scripting, Linux, Git, Figma, HTML5, CSS, SCSS

EDUCATION

Hack Reactor Galvanize | Advanced Software Engineering Immersive | 2020–2021 SAE Expression College | BAS, Motion Graphic Design | 2009–2012 Berklee College of Music | Music Production | 2008